National Institute of Labor Education Additional Records 5944
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Institute of Labor Education Additional Records
1954-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Institute of Labor Education (NILE)
5944
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5736597
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5545: National Institute of Labor Education (NILE) Papers 5767: National Institute of Labor Education Additional Records 5234: Inter-University Labor Education Committee Records
Working class -- Education -- United States.; National Institute of Labor Education (U.S.)
5736597
- Balances Folder 1, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mental Health, Ethics Project, General Ledger, etc, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Evaluation Report of the National Institute of Labor Education, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National Institute of Labor Education, 1963-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- National Institute of Labor Education, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- National Bank of D.C./Washington Check Stubs, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Report to the Board, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- National Institute of Labor Education, 1954-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- National Institute of Labor Education, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Institute of Labor Education, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- University of Michigan, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Michigan State University, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- University of Minnesota, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ohio State University, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- University of California (UCLA), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Hoehler, Fred, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- University of Illinois, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- University of Connecticut, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- University of Chicago, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- University of California at Berkeley, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- University of Wisconsin, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Rutgers University, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Roosevelt University, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- University of Hawaii, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- To be Recorded, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- NILB - Chart of Accounts, 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Nile Survey of Adult Education, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- 1976 Bills (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 1977 Bills, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Deposit Slips, Void Checks Saving Bank Book, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)